Maa-kun!
Where are you, Maa-kun?
He's probably out doing his morning run, right?
Without eating breakfast?!
It's spring, huh?
Time really flies...
You're heading out, Yoshino?
Y-Yes, um...
A date?
I-I'll be back soon, okay?
She's such an open book.
I'm starving... I'm actually starving!
I should've had Yoshino
make something before she left.
N-No! I can't rely on her for everything!
I need to be able to take care of myself!
Shinshu
Wasabi-Flavored
Nozawana Mustard Leaf
Um, I brought you soba noodles
and pickled nozawana leaves.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Do you not know how to use a phone?
You just disappeared for the whole day!
I know you were going to Shinshu, but...
I was worried!
I'm sorry.
The pickled nozawana leaves are really good.
Forget that. How did it go?
Did it go well?
Warm up some cold rice...
Put the pickled nozawana on...
Add the tea.
Ochazuke with nozawana leaf is so good!
That's right! If I want to eat
something, I can just make it myself!
I could do this any time I wanted!
Maybe it's because of the time
I spent making chocolate?
It's time to give it up, Adagaki Aki.
Makabe and Yoshino are a couple now.
I'm in Class E, huh?
Futaba-san!
Class Rep!
I look forward to another year together.
Huh?! We're in the same class?
Whew! I thought I'd be studying for entrance
exams all by myself, but this'll be fun!
Indeed.
I hope so.
Just because we're all together
doesn't mean it'll be fun.
Is that you, Gasou-san?
That outfit...
I'm finally getting used to it.
You're giving me an eyeful!
Koiwai-san is in Class E, too.
It's our first time being in
the same class, Koiwai-san!
It's a whole new school year.
I have no intention of dragging
out any past feuds.
I'm sorry for everything.
Don't worry about it.
This is Class E, and...
Adagaki Aki   Hosokawa Yuuko
Amano Misaki   Makabe Masamune
Arakawa Yousuke   Maeda Kana
Adagaki Aki
Makabe Masamune
Makabe-kun's in our class?
Lucky us!
Aki-sama! Aki-sama!
We're together!
Kaneko-senpai told me to do
everything I could to help you.
Wait. Wait a second.
If there's anything you need,
anything at all...
Is this what I get?
Hey, we're in the same class.
No!
H-How disappointing.
I wish we could've been in different
classes, but we're together.
Yeah?
It's better than not knowing
any of your classmates, isn't it?
She knows me!
Well, I guess we'll be seeing
each other in class.
Screw you!
Hell.
This is Hell!
Adagaki-san, Adagaki-san.
Do you know the answer to question 4?
O-Of course I do.
Seriously?
Can I see your answer?
Oh, I see...
So that's how it works.
Don't talk to me so casually.
It's like... It's like when we were dating!
I'll just do my best not to look at him.
That's right!
I can just keep my distance!
Just the right amount of salt,
if I do say so myself.
Why do I have to hide like this?!
Oh, Adagaki-san!
Did you try this new bread thing?
Gasou told me about it.
It's a limited-time-only special!
What's your problem?
What are you trying to do here?
What?
I wanted to apologize—
Pig's Foot.
Koiwai-san?
Don't.
But I—
Just come with me.
Don't shove it in my face like that,
you two lovebirds!
Koiwai-san, stop!
Call me Yoshino.
Yoshino-san, you're being aggressive.
Not yet. Just a little more.
Now's not the time.
Wait just a little longer, and then...
Okay, here I go!
I have to move on!
I'm back.
You're late.
Whaaa?!
I didn't know you could yell like that.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What happened
to your hair? Your hair!
I just needed a change of pace.
It's not that big a deal...
No, that's not true.
I just couldn't get over him like I was,
so I decided to change things up.
Aki-sama...
You don't need to call me "Aki-sama."
I'm just a coward who's trying
everything she can.
No...
You've got it all wrong, dummy!
I just wanted to play a little trick on you!
Yoshino? A "trick"?
If you want to know, go to the school!
The classroom!
Pig's Foot is there!
Huh?
Just go!
What's gotten into you?
Fine! I'm going! That's what you want, right?
Maybe this is how Aki-sama felt
when she watched us leave together...
That day, I finally understood.
No cell signal...
Total darkness, with nobody around...
Spending eight years up here
thinking of just one person...
You can't call that anything but...
But even so...
I still had to say it!
So... Aki-sama, you do it, too!
Where are you, Makabe?
I came, like your darling asked me to!
For Adagaki Aki
This is what I did before...
Is this his way of getting back at me?
He's gonna regret this!
I'll give him a talking-to he won't forget!
It's so strange...
No matter where I go, it feels like he's here.
I have so many memories here, too.
It's been more than enough time
for "hate" to turn to "love."
Makabe?
Adagaki-san?
I knew you'd be here!
Stay right where you are!
I'm on my way!
Huh? What's she saying?
Don't you dare move!
I can't hear her...
What did you say?
What are you doing there?
That's my line!
Wait, wait, wait!
That girl just can't stay put, can she?
You're in for such a talking-to!
Gotcha!
You made me run across half the damn
school, you gun-jumping rich girl!
What does that even mean?!
Just leave me alone already!
I can tell you two are having
the time of your lives together!
But I wanted to apologize...
You don't need to apologize for dating Yoshino!
I'm not dating her.
I'm not dating Yoshino.
Huh?
She asked me to, but I said no.
M-Master?
Master...
Master.
What? What is it?
I love you, Pig's Foot.
You came all the way out here
to tell me that, huh?
Yeah.
Thanks.
You're always there for me.
I rely on you way too much.
You surprised me, though...
Pig's Foot...
There's something I have to say, too.
But the person I have to say it to is...
I spent a lot of time thinking about this.
Maybe it's a waste of time.
But I need to say it again,
this time from the heart,
or I can't move on.
Yeah.
You need to really mean it,
or you won't be able to move on.
So...
Go get 'em, Pig's Foot!
You're not dating?
Then what are you apologizing for?
When I was fat, eight years ago,
I was sure you'd rejected me
in a really mean way.
So I wanted to get revenge.
That's why I came to this school.
But I was wrong about everything.
What I've been doing this whole time...
Why any of this happened...
I didn't even know anymore.
I didn't know what to do.
I've made you suffer for so long...
But even so... my letter...
Letter?
The one in your hand.
You haven't read it yet?
I was hoping you'd read it tomorrow...
Tomorrow?
And then we ran into each other...
Please be my girlfriend
-Makabe Masamune
Will you be my girlfriend?
Aki-chan!
Masamune...
This is how I feel about you!
Please accept them!
You're sure?
Huh?
You want someone like me?
I don't want anyone but you!
You cut your hair.
You rejected Yoshino? Are you stupid?
Are you serious about dating me?
Is that bad?
And wait, you like me?
I mean, I guess you could say that...
You "could" say that?
Is this some kind of joke?
You're the only person
I could work so hard for.
When it all started, I was fat,
but you were my goal.
Adagaki Aki, the girl who was
a huge brat, but so beautiful...
I'll probably still make tons of mistakes
and screw-ups from now on.
But as long as I'm heading toward
you, I feel like I'll be okay.
So this is all for your own sake, huh?
Yeah.
You self-centered,
self-obsessed, selfish egoist.
So... what's your answer?
No...
My answer's not "no."
Yes!
But are you sure?
About what?
Can you... kiss me and stuff?
Of course I can!
W-Wait! I need to do warm-up stretches first!
Oh, come on!
I'm just... really nervous...
I get it, but...
No!
Five, four, three, two, one!
42nd Yasaka High School Cultural Festival
I'm lighting it!
The post-festival party will now begin.
Those of you who will be participating
in the dance, come to the center.
Once this is over, it's time to start
studying for entrance exams.
I don't want to get separated from everyone!
Come on, that's still a long way off.
It's not that long at all!
That's right.
It's not that much longer at all.
What, you, too?
I mean, we had that Snow White battle and
everything at last year's cultural festival.
The winner got to dance with Adagaki-san
at the post-festival party, right?
W-Well, you know, Makabe and
Aki-chan ended up appearing together,
and everyone kind of forgot about it.
So she didn't dance with anyone, but...
Before, I thought that
Masamune-sama liked you.
It's not like that.
I'm his "master."
That's why he didn't break out in hives.
Because he feels safer
around me than anyone else.
I see.
So I can assume he saw me
as an attractive woman, then?
He didn't end up with either of us, though.
Futaba-san said before
that if you truly fall in love, there's
something that will always remain with you.
There were a lot of mix-ups along the way,
but I think this was for the best.
Yeah.
There was a chance I'd end up dancing
with Gasou Kanetsugu back then.
No way.
I would've stopped it, no matter what.
Even though you were out with a fever?
Anything to dance with you.
Now, once more...
My great wish, my great ambition...
Will you do me the honor of a dance?
Is this your revenge? Or...
My respect. For the Cruel Princess.
I think I could give you the
perfect nickname now.
Want to know what it is?
I'll ask later, I think.